Opening Talk
Yay!
Today's talk is with Funa Suzuki.
Thank you very much.
Are you nervous? I'm so nervous.
I participated in a contest called "Uta-chan" for a solo stage at TIFU.
Thank you.
More people supported me than I expected.
I thought I'd like to keep trying and do my best.
But you said that you thought it was funny and entertaining during the public judging earlier, didn't you?
That's right.
If you say "funny, funny, funny" by yourself...
Is that right for a first-time viewer? He said.
And then I was made to do a comedy on the spot.
I hate being a vocalist like that.
I was a mental wreck before I sang.
I'm amazed you were able to get through that.
Don't worry about what kind of answers I'm going to ask you.
I don't want to be this kind of vocalist.
Your voice is so backwards, it's like you're doing an impersonation of a chick.
That's funny.
Thank you so much for your hard work already!
Now that I've been able to tell you how good a singer you are, Fuuna-chan...
Mr. Hoteison, I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, please.
Can you stop calling me "It's over"?
I'm not calling you "It's over.
I'm Tokyo Tyson.
And Mr. Sakuma.
And here's everyone again today.
They're funny, funny, funny.
Leave the comedy to us!
Ruff Ruff, please.
We're going to start over, so don't call me.
Don't call me that. I'm just saying hello, I'm Tokyo Tyson.
Don't call me that. I'm just trying to teach you.I'm tempted to call him when he's teaching.
Now that you've announced your new song...
Yes, that's right!
9 Revenge.
What's it about?
It's a self-introduction song.
It's a song that introduces each of us.
It's a cool song that shows what we're thinking and how we feel about Revenge.
How was it? Nagamatsu, how did you like it?
I say I'm a diva born in Fukuoka.
That's nice.
I was so happy.
It was a lot of fun practicing.
That's great!
This is also Sakuma's killing!
This is Hajime-san's
Hajime-san's
He does all kinds of things.
How was Fujisaki?
He didn't call out his name or anything.
It's like... what do you call it, Tiger Fire?
It's the kind of thing nerds often do.
I think it would be great at summer festivals.
That's great.
So it's for summer festivals, right?
So they're going to do it in time for the festival.
That's great!
So the summer festival is coming soon.
I'd like to do a project like this for the summer festivals.
This time, I'd like to give you a shout out to yourself to get through the summer!
This time, I'd like to ask you all to think of a message to send to yourselves.
I'd like to ask you to think of a message to send to yourself in advance.
And with these words in mind, let's get through this summer.
It's a project to make a self-imposed suggestion to yourself.
For example, if it were me, I would say, "Don't read the script, Takeru!For example, if it were me, I'd be like, "Don't read the script, stick out, Takeru.
It's so backwards it's not even funny.
It's a real one.
The moment I said that, when Sakuma did this, I felt numb.
I was numb.
I was like, "stick out!
Everyone was telling me to stick out.
It's something I really think about myself.
I'm a little embarrassed to admit it to myself.
I'm a little embarrassed, but I'd like you all to give me a shout out.
Have you written it down yet?
Yes, I did.Well, let's go to each one.
Let's go.
It's what I think. I think I should do this.
Come on, then, I want to give myself a shout-out!
Yes, Natsume!
Yes, I'll go.
I'll travel smarter, Natsume.
What? What?
The "smarter" part is the point.
It's true.
Really? Really?
They say so.
I have a very good concept of what it means to be smart.
You didn't just say it out loud.
You just said it out loud and clear.
You mean you just don't know?
You're a fast thinker.
I spin fast.
Yes, I am. That's why I can get him to say it.
You mentioned the variety of things you can handle, for example, the very old chapchae.
Oh, I see. I see. So it's the ability to turn things around.Ah, I see. You mean rotational power.
I wish I was smarter, though I'm still good now.
It's good now, but it would be nice to be smarter.
How about the kanji for "wiser"? Wise.
Now, spinning?
Yes, spinning. Wise is Kanji for rotation.
You already said yourself that you are clever, so you know that, right?
I could write it. I could write it.
Then, it's open.
No, it's not!
Katashikoku?You're not even being clever.
You've lost the "shikoku".
Kata-shikoku.
Why is the hiragana one showing up?
At least, at least.
Why shikoku?
It says kata shikoku.
Katashikoku.
Then it's more katashikoku.
It's going to be kata shikoku.
More kata shikoku.
Okay, Yoshimura.
Yes, sir.
Even entertainers have to be nervous.
Great.
Excellent.
This is something people might ask you.
I know what you mean.
I get nervous when I go to stuff like this.
Especially at riffraff, because you get to meet so many people.
I'm still wowed by the hotel and stuff.
What's wrong with that?
Really?
Who's the most nervous person you've ever met?Who's the most nervous person you've ever met?
Mr. Bastard. Mr. Parent.
I see... the guy who came to our party.
That's a nice word, isn't it?
I'd like to keep that one.
Let's keep that one.
I'll keep that one.
Saito-san.
That's great.
Yes, I want to be more interesting. I want to be more interesting.
You're a comedian, already. You are a comedian.
That's enough.
You are funny.
How much funnier do you want to be?How funny do you want to be?
Yes, I want to be funnier.
I'm curious to see who this is.
I got it.
Please do.
Like Nakagawa family.
That's the pinnacle of funny.
You're aiming in the direction of Nakagawa Family.
Well, there's one more.
Saito School.
You have to be able to improvise.
He's the devil of improvisation.
He can improvise anything.
No, it's amazing, isn't it?
He's like a big Buddha.
I want to be as funny as that.
I want to be funny.
This is also a good word.
Next, Sasaki.
Yes, sir.
I am
Don't hesitate, Funa Sasaki.Don't be shy, Funa Sasaki
Oh, wow.
What does this mean?
When you raise your hand right away...
I'm not going to do it.
Oh, I see.
When I do auditions...
I tend to withdraw from auditions.
This summer, I want to be able to go for it on my own.
You want to come out of your shell.
Yes.
I could use a stronger word.
Don't be shy.
I think I'll be more reserved.
Okay, next time.
While you're looking at the others.Okay, Hibino.
Yes, sir.
Change from your cynical ways, Hibino.
What's this?
You're a cynical person?
I don't really have an image of a cynical person.
Don't call me a love charmer.
Well, I'm very cynical.
I don't take compliments well.
I wonder if he's up to something.
You're not?
I get the impression that she cries a lot because she accepts compliments.
Well, maybe that's why she can't raise her hand.
I'm afraid that if I say it now, he'll think I'm being cynical.
I'm listening to the radio with Speedwagon's
Itoda-san's show.
Itoda-san's show is on.
I ran into him the other day.
Yes, I did.Yes, ma'am.
What should I do with Hibino?
Oh, I don't know.
That's because you don't show your feelings much.
I was wondering how I can get you to open up more.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
And you're just going to talk and talk?
There are a lot of other girls here.
All about the same age.
They all have characters like riffraff.
There's a lot of funny and silly things going on.
So I guess I'm still trying to figure out what kind of character I am.
I'm still trying to figure out what kind of character I am.
I haven't been able to fulfill it.
So I'm going to change from being a cynical person...
Don't you think you've already done that?
Don't probe! Don't you think?
Don't probe! Reveal yourself, Meyana Hibino.
Oh, that's good.
Don't probe! Expose yourself, Meya Hibino.
That's good. Where's Sasaki?
Did you sit down? Yes, I did. Here you go.
Pounding, pounding, Funa Sasaki.
Oh, I like it. Oh, it's nice.
He wants me to come through.
He wants me to clear the way.
Oh, great.
So, Kazuna Sasaki, the rice paddy is good, too.
Looks delicious.
It's better to have this much ego.
Always a bit from here.
I'm so nervous, so nervous, so nervous.
So, don't have this of Mike.
More and more of them are getting pulled over.
Let me dance, let me dance, I'll get it back.Let me dance, let me dance, I'll take it back.
Hayashi?
Well, get out more nests, Misato Hayashi!
Aaaaah! You mean you're not nesting?
No, I'm really probably about 500 million times worse than you think.
I'm still an idol, so I'm afraid people might be attracted to me.
I didn't want to say anything too extreme in front of people.
I can't say anything too funny.
I'd like to push the envelope.
Don't you think that's bad? Mr. Hayashi himself
I don't think so, but I did think one thing.
He bit into an apple while we were filming.
What? You mean Ryuk?
He taught me math while biting into the apple.
He's a genius teacher.
Newton's betting man.
I'm down, I'm down.
The king of math.
That's the best!
More, more, more.
I'm gonna get some more bad nests out of you.
You can write "more bad.
It's even worse.
It's even worse, Miri Hayashi.
Isn't that good? I don't care if you take out the nest.
Remedies. I'll get it back.
Okay, Takanashi.
Yui Takanashi, expressive.
I don't often have a straight face, but...
But since this is my base...
You're right.
Many of my fans tell me that they like me because I always have a smile on my face.
I've always been like this.
It's the way I've always been.
I can't help it.
I can't help it.I just couldn't do it.
Why is that? Does that mean I shouldn't show it to you?
No.
But you do, don't you?
You must cry sometimes when you're alone.
Oh, no.
Maybe I don't cry much.
You're a firm believer, aren't you?
It's okay to cry.
It's okay to cry, Takanashi.
I'm sad.
It's bothering you.
I'm struggling.
It's been 10 years since you didn't sell well
It's okay to cry
It's okay to cry, Takanashi Yui
It's good, it's ready
Let me dance Let me dance I'll take it back
Okay, who's the one who hasn't been released?
Nagamatsu
Don't be scared, Haru Nagamatsu
I like it... it's good... it's good... it's good... it's got that strong feeling.
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
Raising your hand, for example.
I'm raising my hand, but...
I don't know.
I don't know...
You seem a little unsure.
I can raise my hand faster than that.
I could have done it sooner, but I just kind of wait and then do it.
Like at a benefit event or something...
When it comes to meeting fans in person...
I'm already thinking about it before the show even starts.
I don't know what I'm going to do just because it's there.I don't know what I'm going to do with it.
I get nervous.
I'm like, "Who is that person?" I have to have it all in my head.
When I'm done with the first eraser and everything, I just rush to write down the names of the people who came.
I'd rush to write down the names of the people who came.
Oh, but he's a hard worker.
I do try to think about who was there the next time I come back, but...
That's fine.
But in the meantime, here and there on the main street...
When Arline Peach Black came...
I said, "We're here to watch, so it's okay.
You have a strong mentality.
That kind of mentality is important.
I think it's better to have that kind of mentality.
I mean, don't be scared.
That's great.
Yes, Fujisaki.
I've got some swelling in my hometown.
What's wrong?
Why in your hometown? What do you mean?
It's not good. Maybe.
It's funny.
I used to go to middle school with some of the girls.
I do this.
There were really two girls at Starbucks who went to the same junior high school as me, but the other day...
I walked away and made a U-turn. I went into Starbucks.
I left like this.
I was like, "That's great, they're in love with each other.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm thinking about why they're telling me.
I wonder if they think I'm getting carried away now that I'm an idol.
That's negative.
I don't think so.
You're very negative.
The other day, some of my classmates were at a gathering.
They said something about you at that time.I heard he said something to me then, too.
I thought it was a little scary.
I heard he said he was doing his best.
I don't know.
I don't know how they feel about it.
I'm not connected to any social networking sites.
I just think that if I can be proud of myself in my hometown, then I'm on my own.
I want to be a local star.
It's your mentality.
I'm sure you want to be a local star.
I want to be a local star.
That's a good word.
Now, that's why I asked everyone to present.
Let's get them out again.
Jan!
So many things.
There are a lot of things.
Actually, Mr. Sakuma, today's project
It's not just to give a shout-out to yourself, is it?
Yes, yes, yes!
What is this?
I was thinking of making it into a T-shirt.
What?
Yes, that's right.
This will be a live T-shirt.
Sasaki, get out of the way!
This will be a live T-shirt
So this is your live T-shirt.
No, it's cool!
It's cool.
Saito wants to be funny like Nakagawaya, but
This will be your live T-shirt.
Put your chest out in your hometown
Natsume is so
Make it harder!
More solidmore difficult
Prettier.
Natsume, it's good
No, it's good.
I'm really going to make it.
I'll get it ready in time for my one-man show.
I'll be ready in time for my one-man show in the future.
They'll support you guys.
Fans who support Sasaki
Move, move, move, they'll be wearing Sasaki style T-shirts
That's how you remember it
That's for sure.
So I guess it's a shout out to myself during the show.
Fujisaki, be proud of your hometown.
I'll be proud.
But there's a chance a local guy will wear it.
That's fine.
Takahashi, it's okay to cry
You can cry during the live.
The T-shirts will be sold as merchandise.
Shall we reflect on that?
Yes!
No way!
Fish
Percentage.
I want to wear it. By myself.
Oh, my gosh!
We don't have any shakes, so put that on.
And...
He's promoting the frame.
It's awesome.
I don't want to wear it myself.
So, Miki, why don't you wear it locally?
I really don't want to wear it in my hometown.
I'll wear it myself. I'll just trash it and move.
No way!Oh no!
Megharo, local.
Let's just keep the wheels turning.
I'll go with you.
I can imagine.
That was unexpected.
I didn't expect that.
It was unexpected. Seriously.
Her handwriting is cute.
It's kind of cool.
It was kind of different.
Okay, okay, okay.
Too funny.
But I like you and Yuuchan.
I wish we could do encores.
We can do encore.
Encore.
Worst case scenario, it's okay if you don't want me to do it.
So, the T-shirts that were released today...
Please buy one!
Please get one!
Please, please, please, please!
Please get it!
Thank you for watching to the end!
This time, we have a dog version of Wan.
Dog version woof woof woof!
Woof! Woof! Woof!
Woof! Woof! Mwah! Woof! Woof!